cheapsslsecurity.com 2018-11-25

# Privacy Policy of CheapSSLSecurity

## CheapSSLsecurity.com is fully compliant with all data privacy standards

As a company that specializes in data security products, we obviously take data security pretty seriously. We want you to understand what we're doing with the personal data we collect, how it's being secured and what your rights are with regard to it. This page is dedicated to explaining our data collection practices and the control you have over the way your information is collected and used.

To make this notice easy to find, we link to it in the footer of every page on the CheapSSLsecurity.com site, in addition to linking to it from our privacy notices.

#### What Personal Data do you collect?

We collect personal data at several points throughout the customer experience: registration, purchases, subscriptions and when you fill out forms. The types of personal information we collect is:

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Physical Address
  * Phone Numbers
  * Payment Information
  * IP Address
  * Browser Information
  * Cookies

At CheapSSLsecurity.com, we do not collect or process sensitive categories of personal data as defined by the EU GDPR.

#### The way we use information

We use the information we collect to:

  * Personalize your experience on our site
  * Improve our website for you and other visitors
  * Improve our customer service efforts
  * Process transactions
  * Send emails
  * Improve our marketing efforts

At every touchpoint where data is collected, we will let you know specifically what it will be used for.

#### Cookies

We use cookies to monitor and improve access to our website. They can help us remember and process the items you have added to your shopping cart. Cookies also help us avoid fraudulent transactions and to collect statistics to make your browsing experience better.

#### Do you share my personal data with anyone?

We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to inform service providers about services for which you have expressed an interest and requested additional information regarding that service. We do not sell or transfer your personally identifiable information to third parties without your permission. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive for tech support, customer service, email updates, and to send registered users their passwords.

These addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

We may release your information when it's necessary to comply with the law. We may also choose to release your information to other parties if we deem it necessary to protect our safety, rights, or property, or of others.

#### Our commitment to data security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

When visiting our site, logging in, or completing a transaction, your connection with our servers is secured with SSL (TLS). This provides encryption and confidentiality, which protects your information. **After a transaction, your private information (credit card and other financial data) is not stored on our servers.**

#### How you can access or correct your information

You may review or update the personal information we have collected online from you by logging in to your account, or by contacting us directly. We also recognize **your right to be forgotten**. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to an account or making any corrections.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### General Data Protection Regulation Compliance

We are in full compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation. We take special care to safeguard your personal data, inform you of your rights over that data and If you have any questions regarding our compliance, [please contact our Data Protection Officer.](mailto:%70%72%69%76%61%63%79%40%63%68%65%61%70%73%73%6C%73%65%63%75%72%69%74%79%2E%63%6F%6D)

#### Change in policy

Our policies may be changed from time to time, we will send notification when this occurs.

#### How to contact us

If you have questions regarding this privacy policy or the data we have collected about you, please contact us.

**Web Security Solutions**  
1712 Pioneer Ave, Suite 1322 | Cheyenne, WY 82001  
United States
